(紅蓮)じきに着く。
We're almost there.
Are you ready, Yuukimaru?
(カブト)準備は いいか？ 幽鬼丸。
(幽鬼丸)どうしても
やらなきゃダメなのかな…。
Do I really have to do this?
それが お前の役割だ。
That is your duty.
But I know it's going to make me
feel awful again...
でも きっとまた苦しくなる。
If you like, I can tell Yuukimaru for you...
((なんなら ボクから幽鬼丸に
教えてあげてもいいんだけどね。
That the kind, gentle Guren whom
he believes is the one he should return to,
唯一 帰る場所だと信じていた
優しい紅蓮さんは➡
is the evil villain who killed his mother...
自分の母親を殺した
極悪人だったってね。
Stop!
やめろ！
なら ボクの命令に➡
Then, carry out my orders.
(素直に従うんだね))
時間がない。 急ぐぞ！
We're running out of time. Let's hurry.
How is it?
(カカシ)どうだ？
(サイ)まだ反応がありません。
There's been no reaction.
そうか…。
I see...
さっきの戦いで➡
She used up considerable Chakra
during that last encounter.
ヤツは 相当のチャクラを
消費しているはずだ。
((ぐっ！))
This is the time to strike.
叩くなら今だ。
ヤツに余計な時間を与えたくない。
I don't want to give her too much time.
そうですね。 捜索範囲を広げます。
I agree. I'm going to widen
the scope of my search.
(ナルト)クソッ！ 晶遁使いのヤツ
どこに消えやがったんだ!?
Damn! Where'd that
Crystal Style user disappear to?!
(シノ)焦りは禁物だ。
Don't panic.
I know...
わかってる。
But if we let her slip away,
Yuukimaru will...
でも アイツを逃がせば幽鬼丸は…。
絶対に見つけてやる！
I'll find him no matter what...!
The Battle Over the Barrier
(鬼霧)あぁ…。
(濡羅吏)
もう なんてざまよ 最悪。
Cripes, what's going on...?
This is the pits.
You guys are on the verge of death.
アンタたち
今にも死にそうじゃない。
(鬼鳳)
ケッ お互いさまだろうがよ。
Hah! Speak for yourself.
なんか 意識が遠くなってきた。
Oh... I feel like I'm gonna faint...
こんなところで
くたばってたまるかよ。
As if I'm gonna die in a place like this!
オレらは あのアジトでさえ
生き延びたんだ。
Not after we survived
that hellhole of a camp.
(紅蓮)あれが
三尾を捕らえる封印か。
That's the seal to capture the Three-Tails.
まずいな
かなり作業が進行している。
This is bad. They're well into the ritual.
さあ 幽鬼丸。
Now then, Yuukimaru...
時間がないってのに。
We don't have time...!
おい 紅蓮 ソイツをどうにかしろ。
(幽鬼丸)紅蓮さん。
Hey Guren, do something.
Guren...
もういい。
Never mind!
お前 裏切るのか？
You... Are going to betray us?
アンタに逆らう気はない。
I have no intention of defying you.
でも あの術は
ダメージがでかすぎる。
But that Jutsu will
cause too much damage.
だから頼む もう一度だけ
私にやらせてくれ。
So please...
Let me try one more time.
この期に及んで またそれか。
Not that again?
At a time like this?
そうやって
幽鬼丸を出し渋った挙句➡
In your reluctance to use Yuukimaru,
you've lost almost all your men.
お前は ほんとの手駒を失い
自分自身でさえ ボロボロのありさま。
On top of that,
you yourself have been beaten...
そんな状態で
まともに戦えるとでも？
And you still think you can fight?
That's...
それは…。
今のお前にできるのは
せいぜい…。
The least you can do in that state is...
そうだな 幽鬼丸を使わない方法も
あるにはあるか。
Well... There is a way without
using Yuukimaru.
ただし ことは一刻を争う。
But time is of the essence.
お前が ボクの作戦に
全面的にのるのが条件だ。
This is on the condition that
you follow my orders completely.
わかった。
I understand.
少しでも
おかしな素振りを見せたり➡
The minute you show signs of defiance,
失敗したときは
遠慮なく彼を使わせてもらうよ。
or if you fail, I won't hesitate to use him.
ああ。
Yeah...
フン そういうことさ。
Humph, all right then.
来い 幽鬼丸。
Come, Yuukimaru.
安心しろ
巻き込まれないところまで➡
Don't worry.
I'm taking him where he'll be safe.
連れて行くだけだ。
それで 作戦は？
And what's the plan?
鱗児に作戦は伝えておく
お前は その指示に従え。
I'll tell Rinji the plan.
You just follow his instructions.
(カブト)ここなら
三尾の力も届かないだろう。
The Three-Tail's power
won't reach you here.
紅蓮さん 大丈夫なのかな。
Will Guren be okay...?
自分から言い出したんだ。
She's the one who insisted on this.
命に代えてもやってもらうさ。
She'll have to do it even if it kills her.
この場を動くなよ。
Do not move from this spot.
作戦を聞こうか。
Tell me the plan.
(鱗児)紅蓮さん。
Guren...
さっさとしろ 時間が惜しい。
Hurry it up. You're wasting time.
はい カブトさんの情報によれば
封印を警護している２人は➡
Yes. According to Kabuto,
there are two guarding the seal;
暗器使いと 体術使い。
one is a Weapons user
and the other a Taijutsu user.
They've already gone through
a surprise attack,
一度 不意打ちをくらっているので
警戒を強めているはずだと。
so they've increased their guard.
なるほどな。 つまり ヤツらの目を
ひきつける ハデな陽動役。
I see.
In other words, the way to catch
their attention is a flashy diversion.
囮が必要ってわけか。 フッ。
A decoy is necessary.
わかった その作戦でいこう。
All right. Let's do it.
手前の２人は 引き受ける。
I'll take care of those two in front.
でも いいんですかい？ 紅蓮さん。
But are you sure about this, Guren...?
囮なら 残りのチャクラでも
やりようはあるさ。
I have enough Chakra to be a decoy.
お前は 隙をうかがい
封印を破ることに集中しろ。
You focus on finding
the right moment to break the seal.
(サクラ)封印内に
三尾が完全に入りました。
The Three-Tails is completely
ensnared within the seal.
(シズネ)よし では このまま
結界四方封陣の範囲を狭め➡
Good. Now let's narrow the sphere
of the Four-Corner Sealing Barrier
三尾の自由を完全に奪う。
(３人)はい！
until the Three-Tails' freedom
is totally restricted!
- Yes!
(リー)あっ テンテン！
(テンテン)わかってる。
- Huh?! Tenten!
- I know!
何者です!?
Who's there?!
大事な封印を守るのが
ガキ２匹とは 笑わせるね。
Two kids protecting the precious seal?
What a laugh.
その術
まさか 晶遁使いですか!?
That Jutsu...!
Are you the Crystal Style user?!
対 晶遁班が 迎えうったんじゃ…。
Isn't the Crystal Style Counter team
supposed to deal with her?!
どうする？
ケツまくって逃げるかい？
So what'll you do?
Run away with your tails
between your legs?
とんでもない！
噂の晶遁使いとの手合わせ➡
No such thing!
I'd like nothing better than to battle
the Crystal Style user
everyone's been talking about!
望むところです！
いきがるじゃないか。
That's some confidence...
for a kid from the Hidden Leaf!
木ノ葉のガキがさ。
みんな 集中して！
Concentrate, everyone!
網は 十分に狭まった。
The net is tight enough!
これより 四方より錠をかけ➡
Now we'll lock it from all four sides
and completely seal the Three-Tails!
三尾を完全に封印する。
(３人)はい！
- Right!
結界四方封陣 施錠！
Four-Corner Sealing Barrier... Lock!
I'm your opponent!
ボクが相手です！
でいや！
うわ！
手応えが妙です これは まるで…。
This resistance is strange...
It's as though...
残念だったね。
Too bad.
結晶で 体を覆って…。
She covered her body with crystal...?
《ったく こんな相手。
Damn...
Normally, I'd have beaten enemies
like them long ago.
いつもなら
とっくに終わってるってのに》
まだまだ！
Not yet!
《残りのチャクラからいって
私が使える術は➡
Judging from the Chakra I have left,
there's just one or two more Jutsu
I can use.
あと１つか ２つがせいぜい。
ならば…》
If that's the case!
《次で決める！》
I'll end it with this next one!
(いの)ああ！
いの！
Ino!
《コントロールが…》
My control...
《クッ 失敗か》
Did we fail?
すみません！
まだ 網は破られていない！
I'm sorry!
The net isn't broken yet! Synchronize!
呼吸を合わせ もう一度
封印の錠をかけ直すのよ！
We'll lock the seal once more!
Die!
くたばれ！
今です！
Now!
(２人)うわ～！
まずい！
しまった！
- This is bad!
- Shoot!
くらえ!!
コラボ忍法 ガマ鉄砲！
Eat this!
Collaboration Ninjutsu!
Wind Style: Toad Water Pistol!
うう！
なに!?
What?!
ナルト君！
Naruto...!
(ガマ竜)わ～い うまくいったよ！
Yay, we did it!
That's the way it should be!
(ガマ吉)このくらい
できて当然じゃ！
やっと見つけたぜ 晶遁使い。
I finally found you, Crystal Style user!
キサマ！
Why you--!
《なんとしても
あの封印だけは…》
Whatever it takes...
that seal must be broken!
シノ。
Shino!
な なに!?
あ！
Wh-What?!
封印が！
(サクラたち)キャー！
The seal!
(ヤマト)先輩！
ん？
Senpai.
Hmm?
ヤマトか。
It's you, Yamato.
(ヤマト)先輩の読みどおり 我々は
敵の陽動部隊と接触しました。
As you predicted, we encountered
the enemy's diversionary team.
But they weren't very strong and ran off.
しかし 敵の戦力はたいした
脅威ではなく 戦闘は終了。
その後 隊を２つにわけ
封印班の 警護には➡
Then we split up into two...
I sent Lee and Tenten
to protect the Sealing team.
リーとテンテンを向かわせました。
そちらは？
How about you?
It's bad.
まずいぞ。 晶遁を破る方法は
見つけたもののヤツに逃げられた。
We found a way to counter
the Crystal Style,
but she gave us the slip.
えっ！
お前たちは すぐに➡
What?!
Quickly, go help protect
the Sealing team.
封印班の援護に向かってくれ。
しまった！
Damn it!
《これでは結界が保てない》
We won't be able to sustain the barrier!
(ヒナタ)なんて大きいの？
I-It's so huge...!
何これ？
Wha--?! What is this?!
(みんな)キャーッ！
いけない！
Oh no!
うわ～っ！
なんてチャクラだ。 これが三尾。
What Chakra! This is the Three-Tails...!
結界が破られた。
The barrier is broken!
(トビ)うっひゃ～ 先輩！
Senpai!
Our assignment...is here!
ノルマが出ましたよ～！
グオーッ!!
うぅっ…！
兄ちゃん 怖いよ！
Brother... I'm scared!
なんちゅう衝撃波じゃ！
That shock wave...!
オメエ！ また厄介なところに
ワシらを呼び出しおって！
What kind of dangerous place did
you summon us to this time?!
んなこと言ってる場合じゃ
ねえってばよ！
This isn't the time to talk like that!
目的は果たした。
これでお前らに➡
Our goal has been achieved.
You've lost the Jutsu
to seal the Three-Tails.
三尾を封印する術は
なくなったわけだ。
テメエ 許さねえ！
Why you... I can't forgive you!
フンッ。 鱗児 退くぞ！
Rinji, pull back!
逃がさん！
You won't get away!
うおぉ～!!
うお～！
うわ～！
ダメじゃ～！
No!
うっ… うわっ!!
あっ！
うぅっ！
紅蓮さん… あっ！
Guren...
はぁ… はっ！
ヒッ！ ぐ 紅蓮さん！
G-Guren!
(幽鬼丸)逃げて！
Get away!
うっ うぅ…。
アイツらは!?
あそこだ。
Where'd they go...?
There...
ダメだ…。
No!
ダメだ！ やめて…。
No...!
Stop...!
イヤだ!!
Don't!
No...!
イヤだ～!!
(大蛇丸)カブトめ…
幽鬼丸の力を引き出そうと➡
Kabuto... You seem to be
having a hard time
ずいぶん焦っているようね。
drawing out Yuukimaru's power.
でも 強制された先になど
本当の力は ありはしない。
If you try to force it out,
it won't be real power.
心から何かを欲し
強く願ったとき➡
When there is true desire in the heart
and that desire is strong...
初めて 己ですら知りえぬ
本当の力を出すことができるのよ。
that is when he finds real strength
that even he did not know he had!
これは…。
Is this...?
What is that...?
何だ？ あれは…。
オレ 見たことがある。
あれは あのときと同じ…。
あっ… 幽鬼丸！
え～と 今日のミニコーナーは と…。
大変ですよ ナルト君!!
(２人)大変よ ナルト！
今日のミニコーナーなんですが…。
ああ そんなら ここに台本が…。
それが ありえないのよ！
台本が 真っ白なの！
え～っ!?
スタッフが 手 抜いてんのよ！
(テンテン)現場放棄よね。
伊達！ 出てこいや!!
カンペが… なになに？
アドリブでつなげって。
こっちは 本編で疲れてんだよ…。
ならば！
このボクの ワンマンショーで！
ボクの美しい肉体…。
(いの)そんなんじゃ
数字 取れないわよ！
私の色香で
男子たちを釘付けに…。
そんなのより私の武器コレクションを…。
いや ここは やっぱ
主役のオレが バシッと決めてだな…。
いや… なんか
動きが… 変だってばよ…。
ちょっと！
間に合ったと思ったら…。
(いの)やだ！ 止まっちゃった。
(サクラ)い… 色まで…。
おい こら！ 伊達っち!!
いい加減にしろ！ あ～っ…。
なんなら ボクが
描きましょうか？ 監督。